Meet Max 404. He's a little over five years old. He just met
his first woman. It's time to get down to Earth.
Android is a science fiction, thriller film directed by Aaron Lipstadt.
Eccentric scientist Dr.
Daniel and his shy assistant Max lead a quiet life on their space station, carrying out illegal research on
androids, until they receive an unwelcome visit from three fugitives one of whom is female.
Daniel and Max show an interest in her, but one of the
other visitors has more sinister intentions.
Dr. Daniel, played by Klaus Kinski.
Maggie, played by Brie Howard.
Keller, played by Norbert Weisser.
Mendes, played by Crofton Hardester.
Cassandra, played by Kendra Kirchner.
Max 404, played by Don Keith Opper.
Android is a 1982 American science fiction film directed by Aaron
Lipstadt and starring Don Keith Opper and Klaus Kinski.
The film tells the story of a scientist and his assistant who are working on an illegal
android program in their laboratory on a space station in deep space.
The film was voted Best Science Fiction Film in 1983 by The Age, but
received a mixed reaction from critics and viewers.
The film explores themes of android, spacecraft, escape, fugitive.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.